Munseong Jeong (Leon)

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Profile

I have 1 years working experience with front-end programmer and solid with HTML, CSS, JavaScript also experienced with numerous programming languages/tools including React, Typescript, Nodejs, Oracle, Git. I enjoy learning new languages and development techniques. Based on design experience I am good to use of Photoshop, Illustrator, Figma and AdobeXD tools and analyzing tools like Tableau and Power Bi. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team. in addition, I do hope that I can learn from the best and become a qualified frontend developer in 3 to 5 years.

Employment History

Front-End Developer (volunteer project), Trans Tasman Energy Group, Melbourne

MAY 2022 — PRESENT

TTEG is providing solutions of energy requirements for the large, small and medium businesses. Which using self-developed customer management system.

My responsibilities were:

- Created Retailer, Company, Council and Association list and detail pages.
- Fetch the data from API then filter or sort them.
- Technologies used: React, Typescript, Material UI, Git, Bitbucket,
- Agile mode develop environment
- · Deploy the website to the server.
- Use design tool to create the layout of the website.
- Communicated with customers to discuss their needs.

Analyst Programmer, EASI Australia Pty Ltd, Melbourne

OCTOBER 2019 - MARCH 2022

EASI Australia is a well-known international food delivery corporation.

My responsibilities were:

- Maintaining UI design of the admin system and mobile app, mainly creating ad banners, posters and renewing layout of the app.
 Amend diversity food pictures, restaurant photos and menu (Photoshop, Illustrator).
- Use Tableau to analyze data, generate visualization data, and allocate human resources according to the data.
- Develop and design strategic reporting and analytical functions to meet business requirements (SQL, Tableau).
- Provide advice in developing strategic reporting and analytical functions.

Oct 2019 - May 2020 · Part-time

- Test, debug and fix errors of Web accessibility (HTML, CSS).
- Test, debug, diagnose and correct errors in users' strategic reporting and analytical functions.
- · Creating and maintaining websites, including desktop and mobile

Details

Melbourne, Australia 0452462858 jmunseng@gmail.com

Links

<u>Portfolio</u> <u>LinkedIn</u> <u>GitHub</u>

Skills

HTML, CSS, JavaScript

UI Design, Photoshop, Illustrator, Figma, Adobe XD

React, TypeScript, Material UI, MySQL, Oracle, MongoDB

Data Analysis, Power BI, Tableau, Microsoft Office, Effective Time Management

Node.js, Java, C, C#, Git Python

Languages

English

Chinese

Korean

Hobbies

As a highly active and adventurous professional, my hobbies include outdoor activities such as hiking, sports, fitness and meditation. I have a keen interest in different cuisines from different ethnic groups and enjoy partaking in multicultural activities. I enjoy literature of both fiction and non-fiction natures and can often be found reading a book outdoors.

user interface pages and admin system pages, mainly based on HTML, CSS, JavaScript, W2UI.

Front-End Web Designer, DamingGlass Pty Ltd, South Korea

MAY 2015 — SEPTEMBER 2017

DamingGlass is a global trading company. The core business is the purchase, shipping, and sale of original glass sheets from China to Korea.

My responsibilities were:

- Established online stores from scratch based on WordPress and Cafe24 to enable customers to order products and track orders online, mainly using HTML, CSS and JavaScript, PHP.
- Design and amending product detail pages, model pictures, banners, thumbnails, ad posters.
- Managing product information on different e-commerce platforms, such as NaverShopping, Gmarket and 11 street stores.
- Management marketing based google ads and naver ads, and nested ads in above e-stores.
- Translating documents and contracts between Chinese and Korean.

Web Designer, Sappira, South Korea

JULY 2013 — APRIL 2015

Sappira is a company that designs, produces, and sells clothing for medical and entertainment companies in Korea.

My responsibilities were:

- Maintained product content across different online store platforms.
- Design and amending product detail pages, model pictures, banners, thumbnails, ad posters.
- Creating and maintaining user pages, mainly using HTML, CSS, JavaScript.
- Promote products through Korean actors, Instagram bloggers and Facebook ads.

Education

React Development, General Assembly, Melbourne

 ${\rm MAY~2022~-~AUGUST~2022}$

Bachelor of Information Technology, Deakin University, Melbourne

MARCH 2018 — NOVEMBER 2020

Obtained Average Distinction

Majors: Application Development

Graduate Certificate of Business Analytics, Kaplan Business School Australia, Melbourne

JULY 2021 — FEBRUARY 2022

Majors: Business Analytics

References

Jing Yang

0413 429 286